原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
我叫卡拉·佐·艾尔
My name is Kara Zor-El.
我来自氪星
I'm from Krypton.
我来到这颗星球避难
I'm a refugee on this planet.
翻译     DustD  洗七里  DerbyNinja
我被派往地球保护我的堂弟
I was sent to Earth to protect my cousin.
但我的太空舱被击中后偏离路线
But my pod got knocked off course.
在我到达地球之时
And by the time I got here,
翻译     阿p  左左  C·A
我的堂弟已经长大  成为了超人
my cousin had already grown up and become... Superman.
校对     肉松  饿得慌
我隐藏了我的真实身份
I hid who I really was
直到最近的一起事故
until one day when an accident
迫使我向世界揭示了自己的身份
forced me to reveal myself to the world.
时间轴    想念Gallifrey的Wholock  三水
对于大多数人  我只是凯特科全球媒体公司的记者
To most people, I'm a reporter at CatCo Worldwide Media.
后期     你是不是饿得慌
但私下里  我与收养家庭的姐姐一同为超查部工作
But in secret I work with my adopted sister at the DEO
保护这颗我称之为家园的星球
to protect this planet I call my home
总监     你是不是饿得慌
不受任何人的伤害
from anyone that means to cause it harm.
我是超女
I am Supergirl.
《超女》前情提要
‭Previously on Supergirl...
如果你再次出手
I have a feeling that if you go out there again,
我觉得会发生危险
something bad will happen.
你成了热点人物
You are trending.
情况不妙
In a bad way.
我是劳伦·哈雷上校
I'm Colonel Lauren Haley.
您会在这里待多久  上校
And how long will you be with us, Colonel?
需要多久就待多久
As long as it takes.
你加入进来是有原因的
You joined up for a reason.
你想有所成就
You wanted to make something of yourself.
这是一种外星寄生虫
It's an alien parasite.
它找到宿主
It finds a host,
吸取所有与宿主接触的能量
feeds off whatever energy the host comes into contact with
把他们变成躯壳
turning them into husks.
他吸收的越多  就会越危险
The more he absorbs, the more dangerous he is.
我上次到这个天台上来的时候
The last time I was on this rooftop,
它还跟个空中垃圾场似的
it was like an aerial junkyard.
满是玻璃碎片  生锈的自行车  废弃电器
Shards of glass, rusty bikes, abandoned appliances.
它一直保持着那种状态
Apparently that was the last time anyone was up here,
直到昨天为止
until yesterday.
你是说  你自己在一天之内就布置好了这座花园
You mean, you planted this garden by yourself in one day?
超高速移动帮了我的忙
Well, super speed helps.
詹姆斯  我们正在天台花园里玩乐喝酒
James, we're frolicking on our roof garden, sipping mojitos.
你能收起这张苦瓜脸吗
Could you try not to look so miserable?
抱歉  我在刷推特
Yeah, I'm sorry. I'm just reading the internet.
有好多网络喷子
There's so many people tweeting hate
称赞了守护者
at the same time praising Guardian.
网络就是个粪坑  别刷了
Okay. Well, the internet is a cesspool. You shouldn't read it.
我应该发表公开声明
You know, I should make a public statement
跟这些人撇清关系
and disavow any connection to these people.
你发表任何声明都是在肯定那些喷子
Any statement will validate the trolls, okay?
再说了  任何新闻都是好新闻
Besides, all press is good press.
这我就不懂了  喷子称赞守护者
I don't see how hate groups praising Guardian
怎么会是好新闻
could be good press.
你不懂  但我懂
Now you see, I can, all right?
这些人原本永远都不会读凯特科杂志
These are people that never would've read CatCo.
而现在因为守护者  他们开始读了
And now because of Guardian, they do.
你无意中跨越了鸿沟
You've unwittingly crossed the divide
这样能为我们带来改变
and that is the way to affect change.
-或许你说得对  -莉娜永远都对
- Maybe you're right. - Lena's always right.
她非常有远见
She's very sagacious.
心里有小盒子
Little boxes.
布莱尼  你喝了几杯了
Brainy, how many of those have you had to drink?
-你是说姜汁吗  -嗯
- The ginger juice? - Uh-huh.
十二杯
Twelve.
詹姆斯  生姜能提高我们的免疫力
You see, James, the ginger root kicks the booty of the immune system.
奇怪的是  它还能让我天旋地转
It also strangely makes the roof spin.
军团万岁
Long live the Legion.
看到你这么高兴真好  卡拉
Well, it's nice to see you so happy, Kara.
今天阳光明媚
The sun is shining, the...
看  连大艾莎都开了
Look, the Dar-Essa flower is even blooming.
有什么好不开心的呢
What is there to be upset about?
哈雷从明天开始就要在超查部全职工作了
Um, Haley starts working full time at the DEO tomorrow.
懂了  这确实让人很郁闷
Got it. That's... That's a good reason.
她明摆着是来削弱我的职权的
She's explicitly here to curtail my authority.
她会让我生活在噩梦之中
I mean, she's going to make my life a nightmare.
说起噩梦  各位
Speaking of nightmares, guys.
布莱尼喝多了
So Brainy's drunk.
他以为莫吉托是蔬菜汁
He thought the mojitos were a vegetable juice.
你们上午就开始喝莫吉托了吗
Did someone say mojitos at brunch?
这种派对很适合我
Sounds like my kind of party.
真高兴你能赶到
Yeah. So glad you made it.
各位  这是尼娅
Uh, everyone this is Nia.
这些是我的朋友  荣恩
These are my people. J'onn.
-这是莉娜  -你好
- This is Lena. - Hello.
那是我姐姐艾丽克斯
That's my sister, Alex.
凯特科的新记者
Well, CatCo's newest addition.
很高兴终于见到你了
It's very nice to finally meet you.
-我们对你早有耳闻  -希望是正面评价
- We've heard a lot about you. - All good things, I hope.
詹姆斯说你拥有改变世界的热情
Well, James said your passion for making the world a better place
文笔还特别优美
is matched only by the elegance of your prose, so...
搞得好像是我收买了他一样
I wish I could say I paid him,
但其实并没有这回事
but I could not have made that up.
那你应该欣然接受我的恭维
I guess you should just take the compliment then, huh?
布莱尼呢
Where's Brainy?
他醉倒在一棵杜鹃树下了
He actually is passed out under an azalea tree.
-好吧  我去找他  -嗯
- Okay, I'll go find him. - Yeah.
既然要夸人
And as long as I'm dishing out compliments,
我还想表扬一下卡拉
I wanna commend Kara
她拿下了阿马代·迪罗斯的采访
for landing an interview with Amadei Derros,
二十多年来  这是他头一次接受采访
who has not given one in over 20 years.
谢谢  但这都是荣恩的功劳
Thank you, but I think J'onn should get the credit on that one.
阿马代是我朋友  但他是听说了你的采访动机
Amadei is a friend, but it was hearing why you wanted to talk
才同意接受采访的
that convinced him to do the interview.
阿马代是谁
Who is this Amadei?
一位外星治疗师
An alien healer.
他一生都致力于帮助外星人
He's devoted his entire life to helping aliens,
恢复身心健康
spiritually and physically
明天就要采访了
Uh, the interview is tomorrow,
我需要有人帮我
but I could use someone's help
采访他助手的观点
to get the perspective of his acolytes.
我很愿意帮你
I would love to.
我叫醒了他  他看样子没事了
Well, I woke him ‭and apparently he's fine.
我的长处之一
One of my superior ‭capabilities is recovering
就是能快速醒酒
from alcohol libation with remarkable speed.
还有烤饼吗  尼娅·纳尔
Are there any more scones left? Nia Nal!
-你们俩认识吗  -我们在披萨店见过一次
- You two know each other? - Well, we met once at a pizza place.
你一直没找到我
You know, you never found me.
我当然找到了
But, of course, I did.
你的地址是剑兰大道775号
Your address is 775 Gladiola Drive,
转角公寓二楼
second floor corner apartment.
你的电话号码是5558010
Your phone number is 555-8010.
你每早都会去鲍勃餐厅
You stop at Bob's Diner every morning
点一杯超大杯咖啡  加奶  不加糖
and order an extra super large coffee, milk. No sugar.
好吧
Okay. Yes, that...
他平常可不是这么一副跟踪狂的样子
He's not nearly as stalkery as that just came out as.
你为什么不打电话
‭Well, why didn't you call?
你让我找到你  又没说打电话
You told me to find you, not call you.
我想敬一杯  来  敬友谊
I'd like to make a toast. Here, uh, a toast to good friends,
新老朋友
new and old.
敬健康快乐  沐浴阳光
To health and happiness and basking in the sunshine.
健康快乐
Health and happiness.
好痛苦
The pain...
詹森
Jensen.
你对我做了什么
What did you do to me?
这是送给你的礼物
It was intended as a gift.
好痛  全身都痛
It hurts. Everything hurts.
跟我来
Come with me.
别再靠近了  我警告你们
Don't come any closer, I'm warning you.
伸出你的手
Reach your hand out.
不
No!
住手  住手
Stop! Stop!
我有了他的能力
I have his powers?
没错  你可以吸收
That's right. You can absorb
任何外星人的能力
any alien's abilities
同时彻底摧毁那个外星人
and utterly destroy the alien in the process.
我有这能力
I can do that?
没错  我的朋友
That's right, my friend.
这让你成为了拯救人类战争中
And that makes you the most valuable asset
最有价值的资源
in the war to save humanity.
超 女
第四季 第五集
丹弗斯局长  借一步说话
Director Danvers, a word.
解析语气不是我的强项
Interpreting tone is not my strong suit.
但我感觉到这事不妙
But I sense this is not good.
谢谢
Thanks.
-上校  -丹弗斯局长
- Colonel. - Director Danvers.
我发现你重整了
I've noticed you reorganized
突击队的指挥控制系统
the strike team command and control system.
是的
I did.
你是否知道之前的系统
Are you aware that system has been in place
从超查部成立时就存在了
since the DEO's inception?
是的
Yes.
但请恕我直言  那系统过时了
But with all due respect, the system was outmoded.
以前  从警报响起到出动
It used to take us 90 seconds
我们需要90秒
to get out the door after first alert.
现在重新分配了两个分析员
And now by retasking two analysts--
你去掉了中间人
You cut out the middle men
把出动时间缩短至60秒
and reduced deployment time to 60 seconds,
这有可能是事关生死的几秒
which could be the difference between life and death.
没错
Exactly.
所以呢
So?
我要褒奖你  丹弗斯局长
I'm commending you, Director Danvers.
找到叛徒詹森特工了吗
Any sign of our traitor Agent Jensen?
还没有
Not yet.
但是我们的面部识别系统
But our facial recognition algorithm
在扫描纳欣诺市
is scanning National City.
一旦詹森露脸  就能抓到
So the moment Jensen shows his face, we'll get him.
再接再厉
Keep up the good work.
是的  长官
Yes, ma'am.
借过  抱歉
Excuse me. Sorry.
丹弗斯小姐
Ms. Danvers.
我叫卡西安
My name is Cassian.
我是阿马代的同事  他在等你
I work with Amadei. He's expecting you.
把手给我  孩子
Give me your hand, son.
你几十年来一直拒绝采访
You've declined interviews for decades,
但你却欣然接受了我今天的采访
but you've graciously agreed to speak with me today.
为什么
Why now?
我看到了我们国家正在发生的事情
I see what is happening to our country.
分歧与歧视
Divisiveness and discrimination.
如果我们想要对抗偏见
If we want to fight prejudice,
人们需要了解我们外星人  还有我们的能力
people need to know about who we are as aliens and what we do.
要为别人做榜样
To lead as an example for others,
我必须接受曝光
I must be seen.
虽然这让我很不舒服
It's not comfortable for me.
但我舒不舒服并非现在的当务之急
But comfort is not my priority right now.
你做出的榜样肯定会激励很多人
I'm sure your example will inspire many.
你用你的天赋拯救过无数的人
You've saved countless lives with your gift.
你的治疗能力
Is it true your healing abilities
对人类没用  是真的吗
don't work on humans?
目前来说  我的频率无法触及人类
As of yet, my frequency cannot reach humans.
但是我最大的愿望
But it is my greatest wish
就是治疗人类的心灵
to heal the human heart.
上周有个嘉年华被袭击了
Just last week a carnival was attacked.
嘉年华  被逃出监狱的恶毒外星人袭击
A carnival! By vicious aliens who broke out of prison.
袭击对象可是在摩天轮上吃着棉花糖的孩子
We're talking kids eating cotton candy on Ferris wheels.
他们不安全  政府又为此做了什么
They weren't safe. What did the government do about it?
他们倒是介入了
Oh, they stepped in, sure.
但却是为了保护外星人
To protect the aliens,
人民真理网
他们至少害死了两个人类
who killed at least two human beings.
-只有守护者...  -好了
- And only Guardian... - Okay.
别再听这些垃圾了
You have got to stop listening to this dreck.
这是本·洛克伍德吗
Is that Ben Lockwood?
你认识他吗
Do you know him?
在我重组L公司的时候
Well, when I reorganized L-Corp,
我与他父亲的钢铁厂结束了合同
I took my business away from his father's steel shop
然后跟一家N金属工厂签了约
and gave it to an Nth metal producer.
是谁给了他平台
Who the hell gave him a platform?
人民真理网  某种集团边缘网站
The People's Veritas, some sort of syndicated fringe website.
好吧  这就得了
Oh, okay. Well, there you go.
边缘是关键词
Fringe being the operative word.
我上一次看到本·洛克伍德
Well, the last time I saw Ben Lockwood,
他满腔悲情与愤怒  想让我报道他的故事
he was a sad, angry man begging me to write his story.
而现在  他和像他一样的疯子们
Now, he and every lunatic like him
一起崇拜守护者  好像我跟他们是一类人
is praising Guardian as if I'm one of them.
如果市长觉得詹姆斯·奥尔森
Well, I don't think the Mayor would invite James Olsen
是个社会边缘的疯子  应该不会请他
to be the keynote speaker at his Annual Media Summit
在自己的年度媒体峰会上当主题发言人吧
if he thought he was some kind of fringe lunatic.
-等等  什么  -邀请刚过来
- Wait, what? - The invitation just came in.
我来就是为了告诉你这个消息
That is what I came to tell you.
你该把注意力从喷子上移开
Now, you need to stop obsessing about these trolls
开始写你的演讲稿了
and start writing your speech.
是詹森
It's Jensen.
他现在位于纳欣诺市步行街
He's been located at the National City Promenade.
这是你的机会  丹弗斯  去抓住他
This is your collar, Danvers. Go get him.
超女  该出动了
Supergirl, it's time to rumble.
我不管别人怎么说  我喜欢变形者
I don't care what anyone says, I love shapeshifters.
你呢  先生
What about your, sir?
你想不想和自己面对面
Would you like to come face-to-face with yourself?
为什么不选个和自己形态相同的人
Why don't you pick on someone your own shape?
艾丽克斯  他不再是原来的詹森了
Alex, it's not just Jensen.
他被寄生虫感染了
He's been infected by Parasite.
别担心  我会尽快解决
Don't worry, I'll make this quick.
不许动
Freeze!
特工  去抓他  快快
Agents, get him. Go, go, go.
不要
No!
他变身了  別让他离开你们的视线范围
He shapeshifted. Don't let him out of your sight.
丹弗斯局长  我们跟丢了
Director Danvers, we lost him.
该死
Damn it.
你没事吧
You all right?
你没有向我上报詹森特工不是人类
You neglected to inform me that Agent Jensen is not a human.
他是人类
He is.
以前是
Well, he was.
默茜和奥蒂斯擅闯超查部的时候
When Mercy and Otis broke into the DEO,
他们偷走了一种叫做寄生虫的生物
they took with them a creature called Parasite.
一旦这种寄生虫感染了宿主
And once this parasite infects a host,
詹森就是受到了感染
which in this case, was Jensen,
宿主就能获得一种超能力
the host has the ability
只要轻轻一碰就能吸走他人的生命
to suck the life force out of whoever it touches.
然后那人就死了
Leaving that person dead.
如果对象是外星人  就会吸取他们的超能力
And if it's an alien, absorbing their powers.
我们很幸运  他没有更进一步接触超女
We're very lucky he didn't have more contact with Supergirl.
而且  宿主没有能力
And we're lucky the host doesn't have the ability
保留他所吸收的超能力
to retain the powers it absorbs.
我们会试着在詹森最脆弱的时候抓到他
So, we'll try to get Jensen when he's at his weakest.
那我们要怎么做
And how do we do that?
上次我们用核能让他的身体超负荷
The last time we overloaded his system with nuclear energy.
就是钚
It's plutonium.
我会联系五角大楼收集核物质
I'll contact the Pentagon about gathering nuclear material.
我会去找超女
And I'll speak with Supergirl.
这是一个她无法对抗的恶人
This is one monster she can't fight.
你的决定很明智  丹弗斯局长
Very wise, Director Danvers.
你要干嘛  你应该休息
Hey, what are you doing? You should be resting.
我在派对上举杯敬阳光的时候
You know when I made a toast to the sunshine,
都没意识到那有多合时宜
I didn't realize how apt that was.
但我已经在太阳灯下充满了能量
But I'm fully charged from the sunlamps,
我准备好出去打倒寄生虫了
and I'm ready to get out there and take down Parasite.
我不能出去战斗  是吗
I'm not going out there, am I?
我们俩都清楚寄生虫所具备的危险性
We both know the danger that Parasite poses.
他可以在杀我的同时进行快充吗
That he can kill me and get supercharged at the same time?
这我知道
Yes, I get it.
即便如此  我还是想出去迎战他
But that doesn't mean I don't wanna go out there and fight him.
我知道这让你很沮丧
I know you're frustrated by this.
我知道  没事的  艾丽克斯
I know. It's okay, Alex.
大多数人只有一种方式为正义而战
Most people only have one way to fight for justice
但幸运的是  我有两种
but luckily, I have two.
媒体的力量
Power of the press.
我会撰写并发表文章
So I'll write and file my article.
但如果发生了其他情况
But if there's any other situation,
无论事关外星人还是人类
alien or otherwise--
我知道该打给谁
I know who to call.
不对劲啊
Something's wrong.
我触碰了他们  立刻获得了超能力
I touch them ‭and I get a rush of power.
但能力马上就消失了
But then it fizzles.
那就再找下一个  你要不断地获得超能力
Well, then find another. You need to keep feeding.
我移动得不够快  没法保持自己的超能力
I can't move fast enough to keep myself powered.
帮帮我
Help me.
好
All right.
雷蒙德  自由之子  我们的触角很长
Raymond, ‭The Children of Liberty, our reach is long,
我会布下天罗地网  我们会找到解决办法
I will cast a net and we will find a solution.
人类是不会辜负人类的
Humans don't let humans down.
我保证
I promise.
卡拉  你的文章产生了巨大的影响
Kara, your article made such an impact.
这些评论太赞了
These comments are incredible.
看看这条
Look at this one.
"但愿我丈夫像阿马代一样善良"
"I wish my husband was as kind as Amadei.
#想嫁外星人
#Iwanttomarryanalien."
天呐
Oh, my God.
怎么了
What?
跳过这条吧  总会有些害群之马
Let's skip that one. There'll always be a couple of bad apples.
不不  还有呢
No, no. Look, there's more.
"蟑螂互相治愈   只是为了散播害虫
"Roaches healing each other just spreads the vermin.
杀了阿马代  杀光他们"
Kill Amadei, kill them all."
大多数人还是善良的
Listen, most of them were kind.
但是其他人太暴力激愤了
But the others are so violent.
我还以为让大家看到阿马代的伟大
I thought showing Amadei as the great man he is,
会让人们团结一致
would bring people together.
上个月有一天  我醒来
One day, last month, I woke up.
我醒来
I woke up,
刷完牙  我觉得
I brushed my teeth and I decided
今天不想再用形象诱发器了
I don't feel like using my image-inducer today.
我走到常去的餐厅买咖啡
I walked out to my local diner to grab some coffee
那里有个新来的女服务生
and there was a new waitress.
她长得很可爱
She was cute.
她是人类
Human.
当她把账单递给我时  她写了一张纸条
When she handed me my check, she'd written a note.
"我也是外星人"
"I'm an alien too."
还给我留了电话号码
And she left me her number.
从此我每天都见到米兰达  猜猜后来如何
I've seen Miranda every day since, and guess what?
她不再用诱发器了
She stopped using her inducer.
真是个鼓舞人心的故事  迈尔斯
That's an inspiring story, Miles.
非常感谢你的分享
Thank you so much for sharing.
谢谢  谢谢大家
Thanks. Thanks, guys.
我知道没有菲奥娜
Hey, look, I know it hasn't been easy,
要继续这个互助会不容易  但是
us continuing this group without Fiona, but, um...
就我而言  我很高兴我们能继续
I, for one, ‭am happy that we did.
谢谢大家
Thank you.
谢谢
荣恩
J'onn.
卡西安  什么事
Cassian, what is it?
阿马代出事了
It's Amadei.
天呐
My God!
跟平时一样  昨晚临睡前我端茶给他喝
I gave him tea, as always, last night before bed.
然后就回自己的房间了
I retired to my chamber.
今早我来叫醒他时  护身符不见了
This morning when I came to wake him, the amulet was gone.
荣恩  收到你的短信  我立刻就赶来了
J'onn, I came as soon as I got your message.
出什么事了
What happened?
他要死了  卡拉
He's dying, Kara.
没有护身符  他活不下去
He cannot survive without the amulet.
-我们应该报警  -不行
- We should call the police. - No.
我们团体的人不相信警方
Our community doesn't trust the police.
他们现在对我们的偏见太大
There is too much prejudice against us, right now.
但是荣恩  很多人一直在告诉我
But, J'onn, I've been told by many people
你有破案的天赋
that you have a gift for solving crimes.
我可以对阿马代用读心术吗
Would it be all right if I try to read Amadei's mind?
当然可以
Of course.
-那个女孩是谁  -我也不认识
- Who was that girl? - No one I recognize.
这是什么意思  荣恩
What does it mean, J'onn?
她很有可能是最后一个见到他的人
It's possible that she was the last person who saw him,
护身符也有可能是她剪下的
that she cut out the amulet.
我们要怎么确认她的身份
Well, how do we identify her?
也就是说
Let me get this straight.
你想让我用面部识别软件搜索你
You want me to run a facial recognition search of you.
没错
Correct.
这当中可能有一些误解
I fear something is getting lost in translation.
我的卫星告诉了我
You see, my satellite tells me
你此刻所在位置的准确坐标
the exact coordinates of your location at this very instant.
所以用面部识别来搜索
So running a facial recognition search
显然太多余了
would be the very definition of red--
这就是另一回事了
That's another matter entirely.
-开始运算吧  -是  女士
- Run the algorithm. - Yes, ma'am.
先生
Sir.
还真快  伊丽莎白·霍金斯
Ah, that was quick. Elizabeth Hawkings,
科尼利路21670号
21670, Cornelian Road.
伊丽莎白·霍金斯家
Elizabeth Hawkings' house.
看样子她在家
Looks like she's home.
你觉得护身符会在里面吗
Do you think the amulet's in there?
如果在  我能感觉到
If it is, I will be able to sense it.
十分钟后在这里碰面
I'll meet you out here in ten minutes.
好
Yeah.
有什么事吗
Can I help you?
我是卡拉·丹弗斯  凯特科杂志的记者
I'm Kara Danvers. I'm a reporter with CatCo Magazine.
没听说过
Never heard of it.
抱歉  大中午的打扰你了
Sorry to bother you in the middle of the day,
我在写一篇
but I'm doing an article on
关于纳欣诺市街区变化的文章
the changing neighborhoods of National City.
不好意思  我正在忙
Sorry, I was just in the middle of something.
我还以为你是送包裹的
And I thought ‭you were a package, so...
其实...  不好意思
Well, actually... Sorry.
采访只需要几分钟
Uh, an interview will only take a few minutes,
-我保证  -你的文章是关于什么的
- I promise. - What's your article about?
我刚刚说是...
All right, I said it's the, uh,
纳欣诺市街区的变化
changing neighborhoods of National City,
你们街区算是一个调查对象吧
And I figured this one was one of those.
我恐怕帮不上你
I don't really know if I can help you.
你每家每户都问吗  还是恰好找了我
Do you go to everyone's houses or am I just on your hit list?
你到我家里来干什么
What the hell are you doing in my house?
别紧张  我不是来伤害你的
Don't be alarmed. ‭I'm not here to hurt you.
伊丽莎白  快报警
Elizabeth, call the police!
离我妈妈远点
Get away from my mother!
他不会伤害她的
No, he's not gonna hurt her.
-你认识他  -你又是谁
- You know him? - And who are you?
你们两个  都出去
Both of you, get out!
伊丽莎白·霍金斯
Elizabeth Hawkins.
我们有理由认为
We have reason to believe
你昨晚见过阿马代·迪罗斯
you may have seen Amadei Derros last night.
阿马代·迪罗斯
Amadei Derros?
我怎么会见过他  我不认识他
Why would I have seen him? I don't know him.
他昨晚被袭击了
He was attacked last night.
有人拿走了他保命的护身符
Someone took an amulet that keeps him alive.
我的女儿不会袭击任何人的
My daughter would never attack anyone.
我昨天工作了一整晚  然后和我男朋友回家了
I was at work all night, and then I went home with my boyfriend.
你是阿马代被袭击前脑子里想的最后一个人
You were the last person on Amadei's mind before he was attacked.
不可能
That's impossible.
我向你保证
I promise you.
阿马代绝不会想到我
Amadei would never have thought about me.
他是我爸爸  我从来没见过他
He's my father, and I've never even met the man.
阿马代是你爸爸
Amadei is your father?
失职的爸爸
Deadbeat father.
他从来没见过她
He's never even seen her.
我们很久以前有过一夜情
He and I had a one night stand a million years ago.
我以为我们有了感情
I thought we had a connection,
但当我告诉他我怀孕的时候
but when I told him I was pregnant,
他摔门离我而去
he shut the door in my face.
他说他绝对不会承认这个孩子
He said he'd never even acknowledge the child.
他确实想到她了
Well, he did think about her.
你在他大脑活动的最前部
You were at the forefront of his mind.
肯定是别人
It must've been somebody else.
我每年给他写信  发照片  绘画
I wrote him every year, sent him photos, drawings,
还有九年级的破读书报告
even a stupid book report in the ninth grade.
他从来没回复过
He never responded.
我对他来说不算什么
I'm no one to him.
看你做了什么
Look what you've done.
让她回忆起不快的往事
Dredging him up.
请你们出去
I want you out.
对不起
I'm sorry.
他在想着你
He was thinking of you.
你和他遭遇的事情有某种关系
Somehow, you're connected to what's happened to him.
救我
Help me.
我要干枯了
I'm shriveling up.
不会的
No, you won't.
因为自由之子已经带着办法来了
Because a Child of Liberty has come forward with a solution.
有了它  你将可以夺走入侵者的超能力
And with it, you will be able to take the invaders' powers
而且不会失去那些能力
and never lose them.
你将战无不胜
You will become invincible.
人类的武器会除去地球上所有外星小强
The human weapon that will rid this planet of all roaches.
人类的真正英雄
Mankind's true hero.
钚不够用了  不过我找到了库存的铀
Plutonium is in short supply, but I found a stored uranium.
已经在路上了
It's en route.
铀不如钚稳定
Uranium is less stable than plutonium.
可能会引发更大的爆炸
We run the risk of a bigger explosion.
我们要么把詹森带到隔离地带
We need to get Jensen to an isolated area.
要么想办法控制住爆炸
Or we need to find a way to contain the explosion.
告诉我你怎么想的
Tell me what you're thinking.
电力场可以挡住爆炸的辐射
Well, an electrical force field could stop the radiation from the blast.
你能在爆炸过程中创造电力场吗
Can you create one on the fly?
临时准备一个离子容器  应该行得通
An improvised ionic containment, that could work.
球形容器  可以让电子尽可能地分散
Spherical, to get the optimal ‭distribution of electrons.
就像穹顶一样  很简洁
Like a dome. Yes, it's elegant.
你得有自己的武器
You need something of your own, some sort of weapon.
质子包
A proton pack.
可以当喷枪
Perhaps as a blast gun.
多克斯特工  你能造出这样一个装置吗
Agent Dox, is there something you can create?
当然  我...  当然可以
Yes, yes, I... I absolutely can.
我可以...  我可以用力场盘
I can... I can use some force field discs
把它们连接成力场矩阵
and link them together into a force field matrix.
我还可以配备一把喷枪
I can also outfit a gun to blast--
明白  你被录用了
We get it. You're hired.
我们可以完美配合
We make a good team.
看你们对话很刺激
This is exhilarating to watch.
我这次冲事不冲人
I'm looking at the cause more than the candidate.
-这是个好事  -詹姆斯·奥尔森
- It's a good cause. - James Olsen.
我正盼着在这能碰到你呢
I was hoping I would find you here.
我只是...
Um, I was just, uh...
我的桌子在后面
My table's in the back.
我们恐怕坐的不是同一张桌子
I doubt we're seated at the same table.
这次活动邀请的都是...
And this event is for members of...
主流媒体
The mainstream media, yeah.
所以他们才把我安排在后面吧
That's probably why they seated me at the back.
听着  我欠你们俩一次道歉
Um, listen, I owe you two an apology.
上回见面我的状态不好
I wasn't in the best place when last our paths crossed,
但是现在...  现在好多了
but, uh, well, things... Things are much better.
失陪  我去拿杯喝的
Excuse me, ‭I'm gonna get a drink.
一会儿见
See you in a few minutes.
再晚点见也行
Make that two, please.
我最近在我的节目上谈到过你
Uh, you know, I was just talking about you on my show recently.
我听说了
So I heard.
但明确一下  我们代表的东西不同
And just to be clear, you and I do not represent the same things.
看来詹姆斯·奥尔森
Far be it from James Olsen
不会接受与自己不同的看法
to listen to an opinion that is not his own.
我接受与自己不同的看法
I listen to opinions that are not my own.
但我在你的节目中
But what I heard in your
听到的满是歧视和憎恨
show was full of discrimination and hate.
这时我就无法接受了
And that's when I stopped listening.
看来你们这类人到了这个时候
I see, so this is the part where you and others like you
也会因为无知和刻板印象
start making crass generalizations
做出以偏概全的结论
based on ignorance and stereotype.
别忘了我这类人有时候也会被逼走
And you forgot the part where people like me walk away.
詹姆斯  听着  我
James, listen, I...
我再次道歉  我不想事情这样发展
I apologize again. This is not the way I wanted this to go.
人们很担忧  詹姆斯
People are concerned, James.
人们谈外星人色变
People have alien whiplash.
我理解  超人姐弟
I mean, I understand, the Super cousins,
他们保护我们  算是吧
they protect us, kind of.
但是这个国家最近经历的三场灾难
But the last three disasters this country has seen,
都是因外星人而起
they've all been of alien origin.
现在  守护者
Now, Guardian...
守护者  这才是我想和你谈的
Guardian, that's what I wanna talk to you about.
这代表人类希望
That is a symbol of human hope.
我不想参与进来
I want no part of that.
不要把这些人拒之门外  詹姆斯
Do not shut ‭these people out, James.
你看不出来吗
Can't you see?
这么想的人不是疯了  而是害怕
The people who think this way, they're not crazy, they're scared.
他们需要别人认同这份恐惧
And they need ‭those fears acknowledged.
当他们没有被认同时
And when they're not,
当他们被你现在这样拒之门外
when they get shut down like you're doing right now,
那就会  把他们拖入黑暗的深渊
it just... it drives them deeper into darkness.
让我澄清一些事情  教授
Let me be very clear about something, Professor.
你无法把这件事怪到我头上
You will not lay this at my feet.
谢谢  卡西安  阿马代肯定会感受到他们的祈福
Thanks, Cassian. I'm sure Amadei ‭could feel their prayers.
那会帮他们坚持下去
It'll help them hold on.
要知道我们在尽一切可能
Just know we're doing all
寻找护身符来保护他
we can to find that amulet and make him safe.
阿马代袭击的事已经传开了
Word has spread of Amadei's attack.
他家外面已拉起警戒
There's a vigil forming outside his home.
好的  我有意大利辣肠和蘑菇披萨
All right. I've got pepperoni and mushroom.
艾丽克斯  你在这里做什么
Alex, what are you doing here?
詹森怎么样了
What's going on with Jensen?
他没动静了
Um, he's gone quiet.
这很让人不安  我知道
Which is unsettling, I know.
但这足以让我有时间给你们带食物补给
But it gave me enough time to get some sustenance for you both.
卡拉发短信告诉我发生了什么
Kara texted me about what happened,
我对你的朋友感到很抱歉  荣恩
and I'm sorry about your friend, J'onn.
看来我对他还不够了解
Turns out I didn't know him all that well.
我在报道中犯了战略失误
I made a tactical mistake in my reporting.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我确信阿马代是个好人
I was so certain Amadei was a great man.
我发表了一篇赞文把他写成了一个圣人
I published this glowing article making him out to be a saint.
但是如果我再深挖
But if I dug a little deeper,
就可能会发现他的缺点
I may have discovered how flawed he is.
那些信息能改变什么呢  卡拉
How would that information have changed anything, Kara?
我对于他完美的描述
My portrait of him as immaculate
可能让他成为了目标
may have put a target on his back.
我一直尝试相信人们最好的一面
I always try to believe in the best in people,
但很多时候  这似乎只让事情变坏
and so much the time, it just seems to make things worse.
卡拉  我总是看到人们最坏的一面
Kara, I usually expect the worst in people,
那更不好
and that's no better.
我十分确信哈雷会是个怪物
I was convinced for sure that Haley was gonna be a monster,
但她却十分公道
but instead, she's been very reasonable
特别支持我们
and deeply supportive.
好的
Okay.
我们一开始假定
Well, we started with the assumption
阿马代十全十美
that Amadei was spotless.
我们再理一理
Let's retrace our steps.
阿马代二十多年没有接受采访
Amadei hasn't given an interview in over 20 years,
但是让我们看看
but let's see what he
他最后一次对媒体说了什么
said the last time he did speak to the press.
搜索信息
Lexus Nexus.
阿马代那时多年来
Wow, Amadei gave lots of interviews then,
接受了很多采访
over the course of many years.
看看他身边是谁
And look who's next to him
在所有的照片中
in all of them.
一个声称只见过他一次的人
A woman who claimed to have met him only once.
你们两个
You two.
你毁了我的女儿
You ruined my daughter.
她读了你的文章
She read your article.
阿马代的目标是治愈人类的心
"Amadei's goal was ‭to heal the human heart."
你是说外星人的心  因为我是人类
You mean the alien heart, because I'm human,
他伤了我的心
and he broke mine.
然后你为了泄愤把他们两个分开了
And you took it out on your daughter by keeping them apart.
我从不想让她了解他
I never wanted her to know about him.
但她从我妹妹那里发现了  开始写信给他
But then she found out from my sister and started writing him.
是的  我确保她不会得到回复
Yes, yes, I made sure that she never got a response.
你觉得他那样伤害了我
You think that I would let him get into her head
我会让我女儿了解他吗
after how he ruined me?
阿马代脑中的影像
The image in Amadei's mind
都来自伊丽莎白给她父亲写的信
came from Elizabeth's letters to her father.
他回信了  是吗
He wrote back, didn't he?
你们两个走后  她找了遍
After you two left, she tore the house apart.
找到了我藏信的地方
Found where I hid his letters.
她说我背叛了她
She said that I betrayed her.
我逼她不再承认自己外星人的一面
I made her deny the alien part of her,
这让她更觉得自己像是个弃女
which made her feel like even more of an outcast.
自由之子是正确的
The Children of Liberty are right.
蟑螂们只会带来不幸
All roaches do is bring misery.
你说什么
What are you saying?
谁是自由之子
Who are the Children of Liberty?
一群知道我们的国家
A group of people who know
因外星人泛滥成灾
our country is overrun with aliens,
需要出手反击的人
and it's time to fight back.
他们需要在线帮助  我就会回复
They needed help online, I answered.
我们需要护身符
We need the amulet.
你只会更加伤害你的女儿
You will only hurt your daughter more
如果你让她父亲去死的话
if you let her father die.
我把它交给了自由之子
I gave it to a Child of Liberty.
为什么
For what?
我交给了一个人类  他可以夺走蟑螂的力量
I gave it to a human who can take away roaches' power,
把它吸干
turn it into a husk.
詹森
Jensen.
艾丽克斯  护身符  伊丽莎白妈妈偷走了
Alex, the amulet. Elizabeth's mother stole it.
她把它给了詹森
She gave it to Jensen so
他就能保存他得到的能力
he could keep the powers he's been taking.
那妈妈是怎么知道的
How did the mom even know?
她在暗网上找到的
She found it on the dark web.
一个叫做自由之子的组织
A group called Children of Liberty.
一个吸收外星人的人类
An alien-absorbing human
计划杀害尽可能多的外星人
with an agenda to kill as many aliens as possible
并且吸收尽可能多的能力
and absorb as many powers as possible,
然后让他自己所向无敌
thereby making himself invincible.
我觉得他下次
I believe the most logical
最可能现身的地方会是...
place for him to show up next would be...
阿马代的值班处
Amadei's vigil.
我们这就过去
We're on our way.
伙计  你还好吗
Hey, buddy, you okay?
这个人死了
Hey! This guy's dead!
他死了
He's dead!
那是什么
What is that?
艾丽克斯  我们到了  没看到詹森
Alex, we're here. I don't see Jensen.
但是这里有某种干扰
But there's some sort of disturbance.
好的  我可以看到一道紫色的光
All right, I can see a purple glow.
詹森在黑暗中的某处
Jensen's somewhere in the middle of the black.
好了  特工们  就位吧
All right, agents, get into position.
好的  小队
All right, team.
你们要当心  保持低调
I need your heads up and low profile.
我们可不想引发骚乱
We don't want a riot.
如果你们和詹森有肌肤接触  是会致命的
If you see Jensen skin-to-skin, contact can be fatal,
所以不要和他交战
so do not engage.
让丹弗斯局长处置
You leave that to Director Danvers.
准备好了吗  上校
Ready, Colonel?
-激活穹顶  -输入矩阵
- Activate the dome. - Enter the matrix.
好了  伙计们  我们去找他吧
All right, boys, let's find him.
多明戈  你很有趣
Domingo, ‭you're funny.
你的意见在我们市是比较明智的
And one of the saner voices in our city.
我们需要你这样的人平衡不同的立场
We need people like you to provide us with balance.
可能吧
Maybe.
但我开始怀疑  我们需要是否
But I'm starting to wonder if we need less balance
少一点平衡  多一点立场
and more taking a stand.
尤其是在外星人议题上
Especially when it comes to the alien problem.
我觉得我们得重新评价他们对社会的价值
I think we need to reassess their value to society.
但你是我们最好的中立派评论员之一
But you're one of our top centrist commentators.
你不是他那样立场鲜明的人
You're not one of those fringe people like him.
或许你得承认  他其实更像是一个中立派
Maybe he's more of a centrist than you want to admit.
女士们  先生们
Ladies and gentlemen.
我刚刚听说市中心发生了大规模袭击
I just got word of a mass attack in midtown.
我肯定守护者会帮忙的
Well, I'm sure Guardian will help.
当城市需要人类英雄的时候  演讲有什么用
Well, what's a speech when the city needs its human hero?
不是吗  奥尔森先生
Isn't that right, Mr. Olsen?
-该死  -小心
- Damn it. - Careful.
詹森有护身符和瓦勒良星人的能力
Jensen has the amulet and the powers of a Valeronian.
他走了
He's gone.
他为什么没超载
Why didn't he overload?
护身符增加了他的容量
The amulet increased his capacity
可以比预期得到更多的能力
to obtain power more than expected.
丹弗斯
Danvers?
丹弗斯  你需要增加大炮的负荷
Danvers, you need to increase your cannon's power load.
至少要增加550%才有效
The increase needs to be at least 550% in order to be effective.
但如此大强度的爆炸
Though an explosion of that magnitude
会杀掉穹顶里的每一个人
will kill everyone inside the dome.
我们的操作员有个人立场
Our operatives have personal force fields.
可其他人呢
But what about everybody else?
如果詹森带着他已有的能力离开穹顶
If Jensen gets out of the dome with the power he has now,
我们就要担心更多的人了
we'll have a lot more people than that to worry about.
趴下
Get down!
詹森让穹顶过载了
Jensen has overloaded the dome.
我在重置电源转接
I'm re-configuring the power transits,
但我们的矩阵会在2分47秒内崩塌
but our matrix will collapse in two minutes, 47 seconds.
-我要确保阿马代是安全的  -去吧
- I need to make sure Amadei is protected. - Go.
艾丽克斯  人们纪要逃跑了
Alex. Alex, people are on the verge of stampeding.
超女  你在穹顶里吗
Supergirl? ‭Are you inside that dome?
我之前在附近
I was in the neighborhood.
她不会碰他的
She won't touch him.
布莱尼  你去远离詹森的穹顶上开一个缺口
Brainy, I need you to open a gap in the dome away from Jensen.
-我要疏散这些平民  -不行
- I have to get these civilians evacuated. - Negative.
丹弗斯  你得专注于目标
Danvers, you need to focus on the target.
我专注了  超女会救他们出来的
I am. Supergirl will get them out.
行
On it.
穹顶缺口在你背后了
The dome gap is in place behind you.
但是开口的大小
But the opening is only big
只够你每次疏散一个人
enough for you to evacuate one person at a time.
在整个情况崩溃前
You have two minutes,
你还有2分11秒
11 seconds before ‭the entire thing collapses.
女士  可以吗
Ooh. Miss, if I may?
女士  我能帮你
Miss, I can help you.
超女
Supergirl!
到我身后来
Get behind me.
詹森特工
Agent Jensen.
你没有逃路了
There's no way out of here for you.
枪毙我吧
Shoot me.
如果我枪毙你  雷蒙德  这里的人都会死
If I shoot you, Raymond, then everybody in here dies,
包括你
including you.
我知道你不想看到这种情况
And I know you don't want that.
我想让这个国家安全
I want to make this country safe.
你这么做并没有让任何东西更安全
You're not making anything safer by doing this.
看看大家  看看他们有多害怕
Look at everybody. ‭Look how scared they are.
不只是外星人  雷蒙德
And it's not just aliens, Raymond.
-30秒  -还有人类
- Thirty seconds. - It's humans, too.
丹弗斯  终结他
Danvers, terminate him.
我知道总统透露她是外星人的时候
Look, I know when the President revealed herself as an alien,
你害怕了  很多人都害怕了
you got scared. A lot of people did.
但是不要让恐惧定义了你是谁
But don't let that fear define who you are.
-20秒  -我还是看到了
- Twenty seconds. - I still see that agent
那个我想当他导师的特工
that I wanted to mentor.
我还是看到了那个我傲之为同事的特工
I still see that agent that I was proud to call my colleague.
我还是看到了那个好人
I still see that good man
他很害怕  但是他还在那里
who's scared, ‭but he's still in there.
10秒
Ten seconds.
枪毙他  丹弗斯  这是命令
Shoot him, Danvers. That is an order.
现在投降  你会拯救这里的所有人
Surrender now, and you will save everybody in here.
当一个英雄吧  我知道你会是的
Be the hero that I know you are.
即使我放弃了
Even if I give up,
他还在外面
he's still out there.
"他"是谁
Who's "He"?
我在做梦
I'm dreaming.
不
No.
我在这里
I'm here.
我很抱歉我母亲伤害了你
I'm so sorry my mother hurt you.
因为我伤了她的心
Because I broke her heart.
我不是故意的
I... I didn't mean to.
我从来没有想要伤害你
And I never, ever wanted to hurt you.
我的女儿
My daughter.
没关系的
It's okay.
我没事的
I'm okay.
一直以来  我都在治愈人们的心
My goal has always been to heal the human heart.
而今  你们俩
But it is the two of you
治愈了我
who helped me to heal mine.
-恭喜  -谢谢
- Congratulations. - Thanks.
干得好  丹弗斯局长
Nice work, Director Danvers.
人员伤亡少  财产损失也降到了最低
Few casualties, ?minimal property damage.
谢谢  谢谢你  上校
Thank you. Thank you, Colonel.
詹森在哪个牢房
Um, which cell did you put Jensen in?
我想问他点问题
I'd like to ask him a few questions.
我把他关到一个废弃楼房里了
I sent him ?to the desert facility,
但他也不能说话了
but he won't be talking.
很显然  外星能量
Apparently, the rapid
收回地太快  毁了他的大脑
withdrawal of alien powers flat-lined his brain.
你今天做的不错
You did good work today.
但是下一次  我下的命令
But the next time I give you orders,
你希望你能服从
I expect for you to follow them.
是的  长官
Yes, ma'am.
但我还是得说
But still, I have to say,
你来当局长比那个冒牌货好多了
it is much better to have you in charge than that impostor,
荣恩·荣兹
J'onn J'onzz.
什么
Excuse me?
我们在白宫
When we at the White House
得知了前局长的真正身份时
learned about your former director's true identity,
我就建议辞退他
I recommended his removal.
他试图篡改超查部任务
He was trying to erode the DEO's mission.
招募一些外星人  而不是逮捕他们
Employing aliens ?instead of catching them.
还一直都假扮成他人
All while pretending to be someone he's not.
幸好已恢复秩序
I am glad ?order's been restored,
我们正向着更文明  更坦诚的未来前进
and we're heading towards more civil, honest times.
是荣恩·荣兹招募了我
J'onn J'onzz is the one who recruited me,
提携了我
promoted me,
我所知的一切都是他所教
and taught me everything that I know.
他就是我的家人
He's my family.
他是这个组织
And he is the best director
最杰出的领导者
this organization has ever seen.
荣兹树立了坏榜样
J'onzz set a bad precedent.
但我们会拨乱反正
But we will set things right.
从现在开始  我们严格遵守规章制度
From now on, we are strictly by the book.
这意味着我们要实施严格的等级制度
Which means we are going to act according to rank,
而你的任务  你听清楚
and let's be clear about yours.
也许你管理着这个机构
You might run this place,
但我是你的上级领导
but I am your superior officer.
你向我报告  明白吗
You report to me. Understood?
明白
Understood.
丹弗斯局长  当你离开时
Director Danvers, when you exit,
必须向你的上级军官敬礼
you salute your ranking officer.
是的  长官
Yes, ma'am.
我们一起努力
We'll work on that.
我觉得你还有希望
I still believe ?there's hope for you yet.
我知道阿马代的事了
I heard what happened with Amadei.
你破了案  你救了他
You solved the crime, you saved him.
我既没有破案
I didn't so much as solve the crime
也没有解决幕后黑手
as solve the people behind it.
阿马代有权利去了解他的女儿
Amadei deserved to know his daughter,
而她女儿也应该知道事情的真相
and she deserved to know the truth, you know.
说到这  今天早些有个女人来找你
Speaking of, a woman came in earlier today looking for you.
叫玛拉·纳贝克
A Mara Nalbeck?
说她的摊位被破坏了
Said her stall got vandalized
想让你去查查
and wanted you to get to the bottom of it.
她留下了电话号码
She left a number.
很显然  外星人没法去找警察
Apparently, you're the guy
他们就只能找你了
to go to when aliens can't go to the police.
你还好吗
You okay?
还好  我只是在想
Yeah, I'm just thinking about
今晚在媒体峰会上听到的一切
everything we heard at the media summit tonight.
我知道  这太可恶了
I know. It was so hateful.
我没想到这事水这么深
I didn't realize how deep it went
这么浑
or how ugly it was.
你想否认这件事也无可厚非
You were right to want to disavow it.
我都不确定否认是不是对的了
I'm not sure disavowal is the right move.
我一直在想本·洛克伍德说的话
Something Ben Lockwood says stuck with me.
-是什么  -或许
- What? - Maybe you can't
一味地拒绝  无法改变人们的想法
change people's minds by slamming doors in their faces.
作为一名记者  我得查清这件事
And as a reporter, I need to get to the bottom of this story
找出这些人
to figure out who these people are.
找到他们的首领
Find their leader.
莉娜  你说过的
Lena, you told me yourself.
这些人对守护者感兴趣
These people ?are interested in Guardian
有可能他们会听我的
so, maybe ?they'll listen to me.
只有这条路了
That's the way forward.
听起来很危险
It sounds dangerous.
开什么玩笑
You're kidding me?
有你做我的指挥官呢
With you as my co-pilot?
伊丽莎白说我写的那篇关于阿马代的报道
Elizabeth said the article I wrote on Amadei
让她看到了一个不一样的阿马代
made her see him in a different light.
理解了他所牺牲的一切
Understand the sacrifices he made.
这太好了  是你触动了她
That's fantastic. You moved her.
所以呢
So?
我决定写一个系列报道
So, I've decided to do a series of profiles
就叫《纳欣诺市的外星人们》
called, "Aliens of National City."
我们每周采访一个外星人
We'll talk to a different alien every week,
不只是名人
but not just the noted ones.
不非得是圣人
They don't have to be saints.
外星人和地球人一样  并无完人
Aliens are just as flawed as everyone else.
但是  我认为报道他们的故事
But I... I think telling their stories,
展示他们的方方面面
or all sides of them,
依旧能帮助弥合这个分裂的城市
can still help heal the divide in the city.
其实这是我第一次
That's actually the first time
把这个想法说给他人听
I've pitched it to anyone.
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
太棒了
I think it's great.
-什么事  -本
- What? ?- Ben?
詹姆斯·奥尔森  你好啊
James Olsen. Hey.
我的时机不对吗
Hey, did I catch you at a bad time?
不  只是刚刚我的车出了点问题
No, you just caught me in the middle of some car trouble.
我一直都在想你说的
Look, I've been thinking about what you said.
有时间聊聊吗
Do you have time to talk?
有时间聊聊
Do I have time to talk?
为了你  我的朋友
Hey. For you, friend,
我一直都有时间
I got all the time in the world.
你有什么想法
What's on your mind?